<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dotpad</string>
    <string name="tasks_and_notes">Tasks and notes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_note_editor"> </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="note_name">Note name</string>
    <string name="load_from_internet">Load from web</string>
    <string name="load_from_gallery">Pick from gallery</string>
    <string name="take_a_picture">Take a picture</string>
    <string name="write_your_note_name">Note description</string>
    <string name="tutorial_text">Hello, welcome to Dotpad, your personal app for everyday notes and reminders.\n\n(1) How to create a note?\n\n Select the + button at the top of the home screen. When doing this just click the pencil button to start editing the title, description and image of the note.\n\n(2) How to edit an existing note?\n\n
Select the note on the home screen and a new window will open. From there, just click on the pencil button to start editing the note´s title, description and image. When done, just tap the button again to save the edited note.\n\n
(3) How to edit a note image?\n\n
With edit mode active select the image (below the title field) and select one of the available methods to load an image.\n\n
* Upload from internet: Upload an image from the internet via its URL\n\n
* Upload from gallery: Upload an image from the device´s gallery\n\n
* Take a photo: Open the device´s camera to take a photo (Experimental, the image quality is usually low)\n\n
(4) How to delete a note?\n\n
On the home screen, drag the note to the right and a delete button will appear, just touch the trash can icon to destroy it.\n\n\n
===&gt; IT IS IMPORTANT TO KNOW THAT: &lt;===\n\n\n
Dotpad does not use and does not have access to your notes, photos and files on the device. We always want the greatest transparency with the user and therefore the application´s source code can be found in the official repository for developers which guarantees the security of your data.\n\n\n
https://github.com/bleszerd/Dotpad\n\nThanks for using Dotpad!</string>
    <string name="tutorial_title">Welcome! (Read me)</string>
</resources>